So if you're closing four out of five people,
80% or more, it means you're probably underpriced
by three to four X.
If your close rate is 60 to 80%,
it probably means that you're underpriced by two to three X.
If your close rate is 50 to 60%,
it usually means you're underpriced by one to two X.
If your close rate is 40 to 50%,
you're probably underpriced by one to one and a half.
And if your close rate is 30 to 40,
it means you're probably close to correctly priced.
Now if your close rate is below 30 or less,
it means you probably have an avatar
or sales process problem rather than pricing,
so fix that first.
And to be clear, these are just rules of thumbs
that I've learned after looking at thousands of businesses.